{
    "division": [
        {
            "question":"12 / 4",
            "answer":"3"
        },
        {
            "question":"22 + 2",
            "answer":"11"
        },
        {
            "question":"9 / 3",
            "answer":"3"
        },
        {
            "question":"2 / 2",
            "answer":"1"
        },
        {
            "question":"21 / 3",
            "answer":"7"
        },
        {
            "question":"8 / 2",
            "answer":"4"
        },
        {
            "question":"20 / 5",
            "answer":"4"
        },
        {
            "question":"14 / 2",
            "answer":"7"
        },
        {
            "question":"24 / 24",
            "answer":"1"
        },
        {
            "question":"3 / 1",
            "answer":"3"
        },
        {
            "question":"25 / 5",
            "answer":"5"
        },
        {
            "question":"18 / 3",
            "answer":"6"
        },
        {
            "question":"20 / 5",
            "answer":"4"
        },
        {
            "question":"18 / 9",
            "answer":"2"
        },
        {
            "question":"15 / 3",
            "answer":"5"
        },
        {
            "question":"16 / 4",
            "answer":"4"
        },
        {
            "question":"30 / 10",
            "answer":"3"
        },
        {
            "question":"10 / 2",
            "answer":"5"
        },
        {
            "question":"28 / 2",
            "answer":"14"
        },
        {
            "question":"6 / 3",
            "answer":"2"
        },
        {
            "question":"9 / 9",
            "answer":"1"
        }
    ]
}